It depends on us. The legislation is
there, but it can change.
Especially last year when I was doing
the stage of elevation project,
witnessing all these amazing wild
places.
We are seeing there's these [music]
lands that they are protected, that they
are preserved, mostly because they have
some kind of public [music] preservation
are
on risk of getting private, endangering
the the future of those places.
>> [music]
>> Public lands on public hands. I don't
think it's the ultimate solution, but
probably the best solution that we have
today. Protection, preservation,
and so that the future generations are
able to enjoy those places [music] as we
are enjoying today, but mostly because
they are home
of multiple [music] species that without
this preservation, they will be gone.
I believe in access to nature.